[
    {
        "question": "They know me.",
        "questionHasImg" : false,
        "questionImg" : "",
        "optionA": "I am known to them.",
        "optionB": "I am known by them.",
        "optionC": "I are known to them.",
        "optionD": "I is known to them.",
        "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
        "optionAImg": "",
        "optionBImg": "",
        "optionCImg": "",
        "optionDImg": "",
        "answer": "A. I am known to them.",
        "explanation": "",
        "explanationHasImg" : false,
        "explanationImg" : "",
        "noOfAttempts": 2,
        "questionType": "selectOptions",
        "maxMarks" : 1
    },
    {
        "question": "He invited me to his house yesterday.",
         "questionHasImg" : false,
         "questionImg" : "",
         "optionA": "I am invited to his house tomorrow.",
         "optionB": "I am invited to his house today.",
         "optionC": "I was invited to his house yesterday.",
         "optionD": "He was invited to his house yesterday by me.",
         "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
         "optionAImg": "",
         "optionBImg": "",
         "optionCImg": "",
         "optionDImg": "",
         "answer": "C. I was invited to his house yesterday.",
         "explanation": "",
         "explanationHasImg" : false,
         "explanationImg" : "",
         "noOfAttempts": 2,
         "questionType": "selectOptions",
        "maxMarks" : 1
    },
    {
        "question": "All desire wealth and some acquire it.",
        "questionHasImg" : false,
        "questionImg" : "",        
        "optionA": "Wealth was acquired and desired.",
        "optionB": "Wealth is acquired and desired by some.",
        "optionC": "Wealth is desired and acquired by none.",
        "optionD": "Wealth is desired by all and acquired by some.",
        "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
        "optionAImg": "",
        "optionBImg": "",
        "optionCImg": "",
        "optionDImg": "",
        "answer": "D. Wealth is desired by all and acquired by some.",
        "explanation": "",
        "explanationHasImg" : false,
        "explanationImg" : "",
        "noOfAttempts": 2,
        "questionType": "selectOptions",
        "maxMarks" : 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You must endure what you cannot cure.",
        "questionHasImg" : false,
        "questionImg" : "",
        "optionA": "What can be cured must be endured.",
        "optionB": "What cannot be cured must not be endured.",
        "optionC": "What cannot be cured must be endured.",
        "optionD": "What can be cured must not be endured.",
        "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
        "optionAImg": "",
        "optionBImg": "",
        "optionCImg": "",
        "optionDImg": "",
        "answer": "C. What cannot be cured must be endured.",
        "explanation": "",
        "explanationHasImg" : false,
        "explanationImg" : "",
        "noOfAttempts": 2,
        "questionType": "selectOptions",
        "maxMarks" : 1
    },
    {
        "question": "We must listen to his words.",
        "questionHasImg" : false,
        "questionImg" : "",
        "optionA": "His words must be listened to.",
        "optionB": "Words must be listened by us.",
        "optionC": "His words must be listened.",
        "optionD": "His words must not be listened.",
        "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
        "optionAImg": "",
        "optionBImg": "",
        "optionCImg": "",
        "optionDImg": "",
        "answer": "C. His words must be listened.",
        "explanation": "",
        "explanationHasImg" : false,
        "explanationImg" : "",
        "noOfAttempts": 2,
        "questionType": "selectOptions",
        "maxMarks" : 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Our army has been defeated.",
        "questionHasImg" : false,
        "questionImg" : "",
        "optionA": "The enemy has defeated our army.",
        "optionB": "Army defeated.",
        "optionC": "The enemy was defeated by our army.",
        "optionD": "The enemy has won the battle.",
        "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
        "optionAImg": "",
        "optionBImg": "",
        "optionCImg": "",
        "optionDImg": "",
        "answer": "B. Army defeated.",
        "explanation": "",
        "explanationHasImg" : false,
        "explanationImg" : "",
        "noOfAttempts": 2,
        "questionType": "selectOptions",
        "maxMarks" : 1
    },
    {
        "question": "I know her.",
        "questionHasImg" : false,
        "questionImg" : "",
        "optionA": "She knows me.",
        "optionB": "She is known to me.",
        "optionC": "I am known to her.",
        "optionD": "She does not know me.",
        "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
        "optionAImg": "",
        "optionBImg": "",
        "optionCImg": "",
        "optionDImg": "",
        "answer": "B. She is known to me.",
        "explanation": "",
        "explanationHasImg" : false,
        "explanationImg" : "",
        "noOfAttempts": 2,
        "questionType": "selectOptions",
        "maxMarks" : 1
    },
    {
        "question": "We shall be blamed by everyone.",
        "questionHasImg" : false,
        "questionImg" : "",
        "optionA": "Everyone shall blame we.",
        "optionB": "We shall blame everyone.",
        "optionC": "Everyone will blame us.",
        "optionD": "Everyone will be blamed by us.",
        "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
        "optionAImg": "",
        "optionBImg": "",
        "optionCImg": "",
        "optionDImg": "",
        "answer": "C. Everyone will blame us.",
        "explanation": "",
        "explanationHasImg" : false,
        "explanationImg" : "",
        "noOfAttempts": 2,
        "questionType": "selectOptions",
        "maxMarks" : 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The ship was set on fire and abandoned by the crew.",
        "questionHasImg" : false,
        "questionImg" : "",     
        "optionA": "The crew set the ship on fire and abandoned ship.",
        "optionB": "The crew set the ship on fire and abandoned it.",
        "optionC": "The crew set it on fire and abandoned ship.",
        "optionD": "The crew set on fire and abandoned ship.",
        "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
        "optionAImg": "",
        "optionBImg": "",
        "optionCImg": "",
        "optionDImg": "",
        "answer": "B. The crew set the ship on fire and abandoned it.",
        "explanation": "",
        "explanationHasImg" : false,
        "explanationImg" : "",
        "noOfAttempts": 2,
        "questionType": "selectOptions",
        "maxMarks" : 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Why should I be suspected by you?",
        "questionHasImg" : false,
        "questionImg" : "",
        "optionA": "Why should you suspect me?",
        "optionB": "Why should you not suspect me?",
        "optionC": "Why should I be the suspect?",
        "optionD": "Why should I suspect you?",
        "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
        "optionAImg": "",
        "optionBImg": "",
        "optionCImg": "",
        "optionDImg": "",
        "answer": "D. Why should I suspect you?",
        "explanation": "",
        "explanationHasImg" : false,
        "explanationImg" : "",
        "noOfAttempts": 2,
        "questionType": "selectOptions",
        "maxMarks" : 1
    }
]
